import { Question } from '../../model/question';

export const PHRASAL_VERBS: Question[] = [
  {question: 'Put off means (throw/postpone/remove).', response: 'postpone'},
  {question: 'Call off means (cancel/abandon/revoke).', response: 'cancel'},
  {question: 'Come across means (arrive/find/traverse).', response: 'find'},
  {question: 'Look back on means (remember/recollect/admire).', response: 'recollect'},
  {question: 'Take place means (locate/discover/happen).', response: 'happen'},
  {question: 'Look up to means (admire/search/check).', response: 'admire'},
  {question: 'Call up means (phone/ask/yell).', response: 'phone'},
  {question: 'Come apart means (separate/arrive alone/mix).', response: 'separate'},
  {question: 'Look into means (date someone/investigate/enter).', response: 'investigate'},
  {question: 'Pass away means (let/give/die).', response: 'die'},
];
